<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Resep Roti</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Value">    $7,00</string>
    <string name="Safanah">  Safanah Bread</string>
    <string name="Make">  Make Your Day!!</string>
    <string name="content_text">
        Safanah Bread make from original grain
        original bread make from original and organic
        ingridients,multiviamin bread
        consists vit A, vit B, Vit D. </string>
    <string name="howtomake">
        Get Safanah Bread in your city
        avalaible now in nearest supermarket.
        High quality bread product, nutritious,
        and cheapest then the other bread ever.
    </string>
    <string name="receipe">  Grain Bread</string>
    <string name="bread">
        1. Soak the grains.
            Soak your whole grains and any seeds
            if using in hot water to moisten them.
    </string>
    <string name="bread2">
        2. Make the dough.
            Mix a dough using flour, your soaked grains,
            sweetener (like honey or brown sugar), yeast, salt,
            and more water.Knead the dough,
            either with your hands or with a stand mixer
            fitted with a dough attachment.
            Work the dough until it transforms
            from a sticky dough into a somewhat smooth dough.
    </string>
    <string name="bread3">
        3. Shape the loaf.
            Let your log rest for a few minutes on the counter,
            then pat your loaf into a flat rectangle.
            Then, for a sandwich bread,
            roll your dough into a log that will fit into your loaf pan.
            Tuck your log, seam side down, into a lightly oiled loaf pan.
    </string>
    <string name="bread4">
        4. Proof the loaf.
            Find a warm place for your dough to hang out for
            an hour or two,
            cover it with plastic wrap, a clean kitchen towel,
            or a plastic shower cap, so that the top of the dough
            won’t dry out,
            allow your dough to rise, or proof, in the loaf pan until doubled
            in size.
    </string>
    <string name="bread5">
        5. Bake the loaf.
            Once your loaf has fully risen, it’s time to bake it,
            to mimic the environment of a professional baker’s
            steam oven,
            place a dish of water or ice cubes at the bottom of the oven,
            rotate your loaf halfway through baking,
            and don’t take it out until it’s nicely browned on the outside.
    </string>

</resources>